meetpenny.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy - Meet Penny

MeetPenny.com is operated by Tabitha Philen in Mobile, Alabama of the United States. This website is for entertainment purposes for residents within the United States and no other countries are targeted in any way.

## What you can expect to receive as a Meet Penny email subscriber

I hate spam. My inbox is constantly full and the last thing I want is useless junk. I also hate to sign up for one thing and get something completely different. Makes me angry.

So, my commitment to you is simple… I will not send you irrelevant emails.

All of the email opt in forms on Meet Penny automatically trigger an email series based on your interest.

You will also receive a newsletter once a week by email to keep you up-to-date on deals, freebies, and encouragement as well as new blog posts. Essentially, it is all the information from Meet Penny delivered to make your time online more efficient.

**Special offers from my sponsors**

You might also receive special offers that I have hand-picked from companies I trust. These are paid placements to help me pay the bills but I keep tight control on what passes through to my email subscribers because you are valuable to me.

**Goodies for subscribers**

As a reward to email subscribers of Meet Penny, I offer subscriber-only free printables and ebooks. These offers are subject to change at any time.

**What I will NEVER do**

You have my promise that I will NEVER…

  * sell your email address to anyone.
  * send you an offer that is a scam.
  * fill your inbox with irrelevant junk mail.

## MeetPenny.com Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from http://www.meetpenny.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Two types of email collection forms are used on the Site. The first being the form at the bottom of a post where you can share comments. Your email address is used to connect your account with Gravatar if you have one but is not used for any other purpose.

Forms for receiving special offers (printable packs, ebooks, etc.) are operated by ConvertKit, an email service provider. Your email address and name will be stored by ConvertKit and is accessible by Tabitha Philen.

You have the right to unsubscribe from emails through ConvertKit and to have your information forgotten at any time. Every email includes an “unsubscribe” option at the bottom. Click that link to immediately be removed from the ConvertKit email list or contact tabithaphilen(at)gmail(dot)com.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.” Your payment information is collected by our payment processor (Stripe or Paypal) and is not stored within our website.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for delivery, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  
Communicate with you;  
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and  
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING  
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting:

FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  
GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  
BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

DO NOT TRACK  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

DATA RETENTION  
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHANGES  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at tabithaphilen(at)gmail(dot)com.

### Free Diligence Lesson

Subscribe and receive my free diligence lesson plan with printable wall pages by email.
